let's also do a quiz about the Miss rate
keep in mind that the hit rate is equal
to 1 minus the Miss rate the Miss rate
is how often do we have a cache miss the
hit rate is how often do we have a cache
hit and the two add up to 1 because we
either have one or the other so which of
the following are true for a
well-designed cache is it true that in a
well-designed cache the hit rate should
be larger than the Miss rate the hit
rate should be less than the Miss rate
that the hit rate and the Miss rate
should be balanced as close to equal as
possible that the hit rate should be
almost 1 that the Miss rate should be
almost 1 again more than one possibly or
possibly none of them might be true so
check all of those that are true for a
well-designed cache